{"data":[{"question":"At the intersection for Broad Street and Park Avenue, Kim had the green light and drove into the intersection.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"At","b":"for","c":"green","d":"into","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- For-> of","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"27","type":"1"},{"question":"No one were hurt, but the damage to Kim's car was heavy.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"No one","b":"were","c":"to","d":"was","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Were-> was","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"27","type":"1"},{"question":"When we have guests to our house, we should be very polite to their.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"When","b":"to","c":"should","d":"their","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Their-> them","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"27","type":"1"},{"question":"The Americans tend to be informal while they're being received company or coming for a social engagement.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"tend","b":"to be","c":"being received","d":"coming for","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Being received-> receiving","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"27","type":"1"},{"question":"Women don't usually shake hands as they are introduced to each other but men did.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"don't","b":"as","c":"to","d":"did","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Did-> do","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"27","type":"1"},{"question":"A Suez Canal connects the Mediterranean Sea and the Gulf of Suez and separates the continents of Africa and Asia.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"A","b":"connects","c":"separates","d":"of","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- A-> the","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"27","type":"1"},{"question":"Ships sailing in Europe to Asia once had to take the route around the Southern tip of Africa.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"sailing","b":"in","c":"take","d":"around","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- In->from","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"27","type":"1"},{"question":"She has taken the driven test three times, but she hadn't been able to pass the test yet.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"has taken","b":"driven","c":"hadn't been","d":"yet","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Driven-> driving","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"27","type":"1"},{"question":"Walt Whitman, born in New York in 1819, was two of America's unusual literary figures.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"born","b":"in","c":"two","d":"figures","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Two-> one","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"27","type":"1"},{"question":"He has given freely of his time by caring for the wounded during the Civil War.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"has given","b":"freely","c":"caring","d":"wounded","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Has given-> has been given","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"27","type":"1"}]}